

FACUNDO KOPECH

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

I am a 5th year System Engineering student and I've been working as a backend developer since 2019, using C# mostly but also learning other Frontend languages and technologies along the way. My goal is to keep learning as many technologies as I can and become a Senior Full Stack developer.

Contact

+54 9 349 237-0291

facukopech@gmail.com

Linkedin & Portfolio

Argentina

Education

Software Engineer

Universidad Abierta Interamericana 2021 - Present

International Exchange

Kaplan International Harvard Square

February 2017 - March 2017

Skills

- C#
- TypeScript
- CSS
- HTML
- SQL
- .Net Core
- API REST
- LINQ
- Angular 17
- Git version control
- Azure DevOps

Experience

Software engineer

SOUTHWORKS

May 2022- Present

- Developed web applications using C#, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, JavaScript.
- Utilized Angular, React, and .NET Core for frontend and backend development.
- Designed and maintained RESTful APIs
- Deployed applications on Azure and implemented DevOps practices.
- Collaborated with team using GitHub for version control and code review.

Backend Developer

Banco Municipal

May 2021 - May 2022

- Developed .NET Core applications using C# for backend logic.
- Managed data with SQL Server
- Utilized Fork for version control to streamline collaboration and code management.

Backend Developer

SoftING SRL

July 2019 - May 2021

- Developed WinForms applications using C# for desktop solutions.
- Developed .NET Core applications

Language

English - Advanced

English Level Certified by Cambridge: B2 English Level Certified by Kaplan International: Advanced

Spanish - Native